<Document>
  [color=#897236][mono]──── [color=#FFA500][bold]I. Jurisdictional Authority[/bold][/color] ───────────────────────────────[/mono][/color]

  [bold]Triad security forces[/bold] are the primary defenders of the sector and citizens residing inside the sector. There is a difference between an official TDF Enforcer and Venmar Station security guard.

  Despite not officially being a part of the TDF, [bold]Station Guards[/bold] are, for all intents and purposes, to be considered an Enforcer for the TDF, with a few restrictions:
  - They answer directly to the Venmar Station Overseer and are also responsible for the safety of colonial personnel, including the Overseer.
  - They should focus on protecting the 1200m space near the Triad Frontier Association's Venmar Station and Medical Dispatch, rather than hunting down UIVs or criminals in space.
  - Sentencing and administering sentences should be deferred to the TDF. Station Guards are authorized to hold criminals in holding cells whilst waiting for transfer to the TDF Auric Outpost, with their time in detention being reduced from their final sentence.

  Station security will be charged with Dereliction of Duty or Corruption, should they breach SOP or break Triad sector law.

  [head=3][color=#FFA500]Station Guards[/color][/head]

  [bold]Mandate:[/bold]
  - 1. Protect Venmar Station and Medical Dispatch.
  - 2. Support Sector Command in performing their duties.
  - 3. Enforce sector laws within their area of operations.

  [bold]Protected Airspace:[/bold]
  - The 1200m space surrounding the Venmar Station and the Medical Dispatch (MD).

  [bold]The Proximity Rule:[/bold]
  - Any illegal activity occurring near the protected airspace (within visual, radar, or via communication console and within 1200m from protected airspace) must be addressed rapidly.

  [head=3][color=#FFA500]Triad Defense Force[/color][/head]

  [bold]Mandate:[/bold]
  - 1. TDF assists in areas where Station Security's jurisdiction doesn't cover or Security personnel are overwhelmed.
  - 2. Covers all regions not qualifying as Protected Airspace.
  - 3. Enforce sector laws outside Protected Airspace. Should station security be unavailable or overwhelmed, they are authorized to enforce laws also within the Protected Airspace.

  [bold]Emergency Authority:[/bold]
  - Under extreme conditions where sector stability is in danger or confirmed external threats are enroute to the sector, TDF can invoke emergency authority, placing the whole sector under direct command of the Chief Enforcer to enable suitable reactions to the threat.

  NEXT PAGE --> [textlink="II. Smuggling" link="SOPSmuggling"]
</Document>
