<Document>
  [color=#897236][mono]──── [color=#FFA500][bold]III. Belligerent Vessel's Aggression & Naval Engagements[/bold][/color] ───────────────────────────────[/mono][/color]

  Naval hostility toward the sector and its citizens is a "Zero Tolerance" offense. Engagement must be handled with both speed and procedural awareness.

  [head=3][color=#FFA500]Swift Neutralization[/color][/head]

  Automated threats must be engaged immediately to prevent damage to station infrastructure or civilian vessels. Speed is the priority.

  [head=3][color=#FFA500]Engagement Rules[/color][/head]

  [bold]Automated Drones:[/bold]
  - Full lethal force is authorized immediately. Use all available ship weaponry to neutralize the threat.

  [bold]Sentient Aggressors:[/bold]
  - Security must ensure they have positive evidence of said hostility before initiating a full-scale naval engagement, unless the vessel fires first, then security personnel are allowed to engage in self-defense.
  - [bold]Non-Lethal First:[/bold] Use of Ion/EMP weaponry to disable the vessel should be strongly considered if the situation permits.
  - [bold]Shoot to Disable:[/bold] Glassing a ship serves no one. Shoot to attain a surrender or to disable, then, when it is safe to do so, perform a boarding action.

  [head=3][color=#FFA500]Post-Engagement[/color][/head]

  Once a naval threat is neutralized:
  - [bold]Search for Survivors:[/bold] Board the vessel to apprehend any remaining hostiles.
  - [bold]Offender's Ship:[/bold] The offending ship must be towed to dock with the Auric Outpost and to be held there for the duration of the offender's brig time. TDF docks should be used over civilian docks if they are available. Once they are docked, if the severity of the sentence results in a capital punishment or cryogenic storage, contact TDF High Command to handle the offenders ship and it will be handled per the arrest procedures.
  - Arrest the offender.

  NEXT PAGE --> [textlink="IV. Arrest Procedure" link="SOPPostArrestProcedure"]
</Document>
