<Document>
[color=#ffff00][head=3]Section 1: Use of Language and Respect[/head][/color]

[color=#a4885c]1.1[/color] Use English as your primary method of communication. You may talk in other languages briefly but avoid partaking in longer conversations in another language.  *

[color=#a4885c]1.2[/color] Using any OOC channel (OOC/LOOC/SOOC/Ghost chat) to insult or belittle another player, their ingame conduct, or OOC conduct in any way is forbidden.  [color=#f1c232]★★[/color]

[color=#a4885c]1.3[/color] We have a Zero Tolerance policy for any intentional slurs, hate speech, bigotry, racism, speciesism, sexism, or ableism. Any terms that use real or implied mental or physical disabilities to mock or denigrate players or their characters are prohibited. Unintentional incidents will be handled with more care. Repeated incidents will be looked upon worse.  [color=#cc0000]★★★[/color]

[color=#a4885c]1.4[/color] Do not intentionally create unnecessary conflict or disruption without reasonable in-character justification. [color=#f1c232]★★[/color]

[color=#a4885c]1.5[/color] Respect others OOC consent, dignity and boundaries. Any incident of being asked to stop in any OOC channel must be met with an immediate agreement and ceasing of the upsetting action. If you feel this rule is abused for gameplay advantages, please ahelp. [color=#cc0000]★★★[/color]

[color=#a4885c]1.6[/color] Do not spam or advertise other servers, products, services or otherwise for OOC content. You are permitted to advertise your IC shop, services, and so forth in character. [color=#f1c232]★★[/color]

[color=#a4885c]1.7[/color] Privacy holobarriers must be used to designate any area that is being used for private or NSFW roleplay that requires consent to view. [color=#cc0000]★★★[/color]

  - [color=#a4885c]1.7A[/color] The description on the holobarrier must clearly state whether the area is public/open or private/invite-only. If there is no clear description, assume it is private.

  - [color=#a4885c]1.7B[/color] Entering a public area cordoned off by a privacy holobarrier, automatically grants consent to view NSFW content contained within.  Agreeing to abide by the terms in the holobarrier description. Additional explicit consent is required before participating in any NSFW activity.

  - [color=#a4885c]1.7C[/color] Never open a bolted door with someone else's privacy holobarrier on it.

  - [color=#a4885c]1.7D[/color] Do not hide contraband or other antagonistic activity behind a holobarrier.  Keep all antagonistic activity in a location publicly accessible.
</Document>
