<Document>
[color=#ffff00][head=3]Section 8: Erotic/Extreme Roleplay Rules[/head][/color]

[color=#FFFACD]We are an 18+ server with an explicit welcoming to mature themes and the full range of performed gender and sexuality: Extreme content is not necessarily just sexual; but can include dismemberment outside of medical/surgical contexts or other extreme violence. What is performed in the complete privacy of Subtle Emotes will not be audited unless directly relevant to a ticket.[/color]

[color=#a4885c]8.1[/color] ERP does not take priority over Command, Security, EMS, or faction roles. If you are requested or needed, you must respond and return to your duties immediately.  [color=#f1c232]★★[/color]

[color=#a4885c]8.2[/color] Do not use ERP, or the offer of ERP, as a means of forwarding any antagonistic goals without OOC consent from those involved. ★

[color=#a4885c]8.3[/color] Do not shame others for the kinks they enjoy, or actions that happen in private. ★

[color=#a4885c]8.4[/color] You must use Subtle, Whisper, and Subtle OOC for any and all erotic or extreme roleplay material. [color=#cc0000]★★★[/color]

  - [color=#a4885c]8.4A[/color] Do not engage in, or discuss, extreme or sexual topics in any public setting. This includes privately informing people of previous extreme or erotic scenes without consulting all parties involved beforehand.

  - [color=#a4885c]8.4B[/color] Extreme or erotic scenes involving CNC or similar themes should never be reported as crimes.

  -  [color=#a4885c]8.4C[/color] Do not involve anyone in suicide RP outside of consenting parties. This includes medical implants announcing the scene to non-consenting parties.

[color=#a4885c]8.5[/color] Radio, Handicomms, and Local are visible to ghosted players. Without the ability to "walk away" from content they find objectionable or do not wish to engage with, keep anything above mild to moderate innuendo to Whisper or Subtle. ★

  -  [color=#a4885c]8.5A[/color] Sexual implications or risqué banter are acceptable.

  -  [color=#a4885c]8.5B[/color] Visceral descriptions or promises of BDSM-coded degradation are not permitted.

  - [color=#a4885c]8.5C[/color] Turn off devices that can transmit voices (shuttle consoles, Handicomms, etc.) to avoid disturbing other players and ghosts.

[color=#a4885c]8.6[/color] Engaging in ERP with a non-sentient creature is prohibited. This includes creatures that resemble any real-world animal, regardless of whether they have been made sentient using Cognizine. [color=#cc0000]★★★[/color]

  -  [color=#a4885c]8.6A[/color] This includes spiders, carp/sharkminnows, station pets or emotional support animals, mice, mothroaches, bats, monkeys, and similar creatures.

  - [color=#a4885c]8.6B[/color] This does not include silicons, xenos, full-sized dragons, slimes, flesh monsters, kobolds, and similar sentient species.

[color=#a4885c]8.7[/color] When roleplaying another person's character, OOC consent from the original owner of the character is required before engaging in ERP. [color=#f1c232]★★[/color]

[color=#a4885c]8.8[/color] You are not permitted to ERP in public. You must be in a location with a reasonable expectation of privacy, such as your ship, or behind bolted or welded doors. [color=#f1c232]★★[/color]
</Document>
