<Document>
[color=#ffff00][head=3]Section 11: Ship Saving and Design[/head][/color]

[color=#a4885c]11.1[/color] Ships are to be no larger than 80×50 tiles. ★

[color=#a4885c]11.2[/color] Do not abuse the ship save mechanic to avoid in-character consequences. [color=#f1c232]★★[/color]

[color=#a4885c]11.3[/color] Do not exploit the stash to duplicate items.  [color=#cc0000]★★★[/color]

[color=#a4885c]11.4[/color] Ship backups are only to be used in the event of bugs, server issues, or other OOC problems. Loading backups may only be done with admin permission. Request this through an ahelp in-game or a ticket on the Discord. [color=#f1c232]★★[/color]

  -  [color=#a4885c]11.4A[/color] You may not load a ship backup if your ship was destroyed by hostile elements such as automated defenses or offenses (Drones, LPBs, etc.).

  -  [color=#a4885c]11.4B[/color] You may not load from a backup if your ship deed was lost. Recover that ship through IC means.

  -  [color=#a4885c]11.4C[/color] Any ship that was not saved due to player negligence is not entitled to compensation from the administration for loss of progress when loading a backup. An ahelp is still required.

[color=#a4885c]11.5[/color] Thrusters should be in a position where it is possible to hit them with ship weapons.  There should be no entities (except for 2 grilles) that block the path of thrusters being shot from another ship. [color=#f1c232]★★[/color]

  - [color=#a4885c]11.5A[/color] Thrusters should not be placed at the exhaust of another thruster.

  - [color=#a4885c]11.5B[/color] For more information, refer to Thruster Placement in Discord → Admin Questions → Thruster Placement.

[color=#a4885c]11.6[/color] Creation of any system that causes server lag is not allowed. Any player who owns such a setup will be given a single warning to remove it if it causes server lag. [color=#f1c232]★★[/color]

[color=#a4885c]11.7[/color] Directional fans should be utilised at airlocks, to create cargo bays, or other fashions you would find in a ship from a Shipyard.  Not as replacements for ship structural design (walls, windows, and all variations thereof). [color=#f1c232]★★[/color]
</Document>
